toothless.
无牙
Are you okay, bud?
你没事吧 伙计
Oh, I am so sorry, toothless.
真是太对不起你了 无牙
This was all my fault.
都是我的错
-Whoa. What's the matter, bud?  - Hey there! Boy!
-伙计 怎么回事 - 嘿 看这儿 伙计
You weren't gonna leave  Before we finished our business, were you
在解决我们的恩怨之前  你不该走的 不是吗
That's what I would expect from stoick's little runt.
这才是史图伊克的好儿子
- Oh, boy  - Hiccup!
- 哦 拜托  - 嗝嗝
Hiccup, no! We got what we came for!
别去 嗝嗝!我们刚找到你
Do it, boy. I'm right here!
-来抓我吧 小子 我就在这儿
Now!
动手
- He's down!  - Dragons, everybody.
- 他被抓住了  - 上龙  大伙儿
Uh, would love to, but as you can see--
我也想去 只是你看—
Trusting dragons. This is what it gets you.
相信龙  结果就是这样
Wait. Look!
等等 看
- Yeah, we taught him that!  We didn't teach them that, did we?
- 我们教过他的 -没有吧
I didn't think so.
真没有
What happened?
发生什么了
The dragons saved you on their own.
飞龙们自发去救你